What is Amanda talking about, y'all? Cuz
Amanda is up here. What is Amanda
talking about?
And y'all know we just finished kind of
going in on Amanda, you know, what that
was last week because of her comments
about Cheyenne Bryant. Like, she's not
harming anybody by lying about her
credentials. She's not harming anybody
by lying about her credentials. I mean,
yeah, you know, she's pretending to be a
therapist, and you know, that can cause
people to get depressed working with a
therapist who doesn't know what the [ __ ]
they're talking about. Like, [snorts]
what's up with Amanda? Let's hear. Oh,
oh, wait. No, we didn't.
No, we didn't, girl. No, we didn't
almost make you take your own life.
Wait, let me let me Yeah, y'all can't I
don't think y'all could hear that. Hold
up.
Let [snorts] me let me fix this sound
right quick. Sinuses, y'all. Allergies.
Too much.
Okay, hold up. Let me see.
>> into thinking that I wasn't a likable
girl and that I didn't deserve to live.
You almost got me.
Almost got me. Wasn't going to happen
again.
It wasn't going to happen again.
In 2020, I really, really, really
thought
I don't belong here.
I mean, I'm not from here.
And I really thought, "Okay, well, you
know,
it's time to go."
Anybody here who's ever had suicidal
ideations
knows that
it's a very
The way that It's an out-of-body kind of
experience because
there's like it's like the angel on the
shoulder on your the angel and the devil
on your shoulder arguing, right? Cuz
part of you is like, "Nah, like, you
good." And then the other part of you is
like, "It's not about you being good.
This [ __ ] ain't good. This [ __ ] ain't
good. This [ __ ] ain't good."
You know? And and and sometimes it's
like,
"Yeah, it's time to go."
I had again listen to my intuition when
it said, "You need to get a psychiatrist
because you need to get on meds."
And I could have ignored that and played
into
the social nonsense that tells you that
that's not going to be something that
you need to do because, you know, of
Like I remember I told a homegirl that I
had to get on meds and she was like,
"Oh, you should have told me. I would
have prayed for you so that you didn't
have to." We're not homegirls anymore
cuz that's the dumbest [ __ ] out.
Um
However, I know that I'm in Babylon.
I [snorts] know where I'm at. I'm in
chaos. My soul is not
meant to stay here forever, but while it
is here in this space, in this
particular part of this planet,
it needs some help.
And so I be on my Lexapro.
Y'all almost made me take my own life
cuz you almost tricked me into thinking
that I wasn't a likable broad and that I
didn't deserve to live.
You almost got me.
Okay, so Katie, I'm going to say this.
The law is always on your side. Um
>> [snorts]
>> Drop the reference.
Uh
I'mma say this, y'all. Being Being I
don't think being Amanda Seales is easy.
Uh I'm going to have some empathy and
compassion and act like the evolved
grown adult person that I am and say
that it's very difficult when you say
[ __ ] online that people don't like. And
people There are some people that's just
like, "Oh girl, shut the [ __ ] up."
Right? But there are other people that
are sending you death threats and
telling you to kill yourself and telling
you you have no value in life and nobody
likes you. Why are you here?
They project their own self-hate onto a
person because the person is an easy
target.
>> [snorts]
>> And so I'm going to say that no, Amanda,
I don't always agree.
Nobody does. I even hate that I have to
say that because duh, [ __ ]
But what I'mma say is that
you said something people didn't agree
with.
It probably
Thank you, copy and paste. It probably
was very difficult to deal with the way
people was coming at you about it.
>> [snorts]
>> Um especially after you respond telling
us you ain't give a [ __ ] Which is, you
know, I would say the same thing and
then I would probably would still cry
about it later in the shower because
[ __ ] I got to get this [ __ ] off my
chest.
Lexapro [snorts] helps.
I used to be on Lexapro, y'all.
And then I decided
>> [snorts]
>> Why am I doing Lexapro?
I can just smoke the tweeds.
You know what I mean?
Seems healthier. Lexapro
shuts down a part of your brain. And oh
my god, y'all.
When you be getting off Lexapro because
it shuts down a part of your brain, you
have to go through brain zings. And when
I would get was getting off of it and I
was going through brain zings, I was
just like, yeah, son, this crazy. I'm
probably not going to do this [ __ ]
again. I would just go ahead and [ __ ]
with Mary until it's all said and done
because first of all, [ __ ] you [ __ ]
with my orgasms. Now you're doing too
much.
And yeah, so you know, listen.
I know we don't always like Amanda. But
Amanda is a human. Amanda hasn't like
actively hurt anybody. You know what I'm
saying? The same thing she was saying
about Cheyenne and Brian, I'mma say
about her even though I feel like she
was wrong about Cheyenne.
I don't see her giving advice to people
that, you know, that is from a space
where they feel like they have to take
it because you're a therapist or some
[ __ ] No, people just either [ __ ] with
you or they don't [ __ ] with you. People
either want to be fanatics, stans or
they just, you know, they [ __ ] with you
casually. Whatever the situation is,
I don't ever want somebody to feel,
especially Amanda, cuz I do feel like
Amanda is on the spectrum and Amanda
does have [ __ ] about her what it's like
please don't take it that deep. But I do
understand the suicidal ideations
especially at a time like this.
>> [snorts]
>> So you know this is just a moment y'all.
This is just a moment where you could
feel like somebody is trying to get
attention but also I feel like it's a
time where somebody is trying to recover
from you know some form of [ __ ] evil
ego death because of the way y'all like
to eat people up on social media.
I have empathy for that cuz I feel like
everybody talk [ __ ] at the end of the
day but the way you have to deal with
sometimes hundreds of thousands of
people talking [ __ ] to you maybe
sometimes millions of people talking
[ __ ] to you.
It's not easy for anyone person to deal
with. It's not easy for anyone person
psyche to deal with the in and you know
the inundated uh comments about you from
people that don't even know you. I don't
care if some of the [ __ ] is true. It's
not [ __ ] easy to deal with. You know
what I mean? And you know
as somebody that has had size suicidal
ideations throughout my life
consistently
um to not be in that space anymore I'm
grateful for not being in that space but
I always remember what it felt like and
so when people are going through that I
find myself wanting to have
empathy for them.
And so while
she disappointed me
I still don't want her to be in that
space. So I wish her all the best. I
wish her health okay? And I you know I
wish her the ability to just you know
get your ass off the [ __ ] internet
and recover. Everybody will forget soon
enough but I understand it's hard out
here.
>> It's your girl Bonnie Blue so let's go
ahead let's go ahead